A Guide to the American Public Transportation Association Collection
Copyright George Mason University Libraries
- American Public Transportation Association Collection
  - 900.01 TENNESSEE PUBLIC TRANSIT DIRECTORY (Box Box 46)
  - 900.01 MEMPHIS, TN (Box Box 46)
  - 900.01 SOUTH DAKOTA (GENERAL) (Box Box 46)
  - 900.01 SOUTH CAROLINA (GENERAL) (Box Box 46)
  - 900.01 TEXAS (GENERAL) (Box Box 46)
  - 900.01 AUSTIN-TEXAS (Box Box 46)
  - 900.01 METROPOLITAN TRANSIT AUTHORITY (NASHVILLE) (Box Box 46)
  - 900.01 FOREIGN MOTOR BUS OPERATIONS (Box Box 46)
  - 900.01 NEW MEXICO (Box Box 46)
  - 900.01 SAN ANTONIO PUBLIC SERVICE COMPANY (Box Box 46)
  - 900.01 VIRGINIA (GENERAL) (Box Box 46)
  - 900.01 UTAH (GENERAL) (Box Box 46)
  - 900.01 LUZERNE COUNTY TRANSPORTATION AUTHORITY (Box Box 46)
  - 900.01 BERKS AREA READING TRANSPORTATION AUTHORITY (Box Box 46)
  - 900.01 PENNSYLVANIA (GENERAL) (Box Box 46)
  - 900.01 ERIE METROPOLITAN TRANSIT AUTHORITY (Box Box 46)
  - 900.01 WEST VIRGINIA (Box Box 46)
  - 900.01 VIRGINIA (GENERAL) (Box Box 46)
  - D.O.T./U.M.T.A. (Box Box 47)
  - Statements/Conference Reports (Box Box 47)
  - Statements/Conference Reports (Box Box 47)
  - Task Force G (Box Box 47)
  - 814.8 Federal Aid Highway Act (5.502) Task Force G (Box Box 47)
  - H.R. Report (Box Box 47)
  - H.R. Report (Box Box 47)
  - Highway Bill/Highway Fund (Box Box 47)
  - Statement from A. Transit Association and Statement from Senator (Box Box 47)
  - Rail and Bus Transit/Federal Highway Act. (Box Box 47)
  - Highway Trust Fund (Box Box 47)
  - Federal Aid Highway and Mass Transit Act (Box Box 47)
  - Highway Act of 1970 (Box Box 47)
  - Highway Act of 1970 (Box Box 47)
  - Highway Act of 1970 (Box Box 47)
  - Highway Act of 1970 (Box Box 47)
  - Highway Act of 1970 (Box Box 47)
  - Highway Act of 1970 (Box Box 47)
  - Highway Cost Allocation Study (Box Box 47)
  - Highway Cost Allocation Study (Box Box 47)
  - Federal Aid Highway Act of 1956 (Box Box 48)
  - Federal Aid Highway Act of 1956 (Box Box 48)
  - Fuel Tax File (Box Box 48)
  - 814.8 WO Inf. Public Works Planning (Box Box 48)
  - Taxation and Finance (Box Box 48)
  - Taxation ad Finance (Box Box 48)
  - 814.8 WoInf Section 210 Highway Act (Box Box 48)
  - Section 210 Highway Act (Box Box 48)
  - Section 210 Highway Act. (Box Box 48)
  - Federal Aid Highway Act of 1972 (Box Box 48)
  - Housing and Urban Development Act of 1972 (Box Box 48)
  - 900.02 PITTSBURG (Box Box 49)
  - 900.02 WISCONSIN (Box Box 49)
  - 900.02 WASHINGTON (Box Box 49)
  - 900.02 TEXAS (Box Box 49)
  - 900.02 UTAH (Box Box 49)
  - 900.02 VIRGINIA (Box Box 49)
  - 900.02 TENNESSEE (Box Box 49)
  - 900.02 SOUTH CAROLINA (Box Box 49)
  - 900.02 RHODE ISLAND (Box Box 49)
  - 900.02 TRAIN BUS SERVICE (Box Box 49)
  - 900.013 DISCONTINUED LINES (Box Box 49)
  - 900.013 DISCONTINUED LINES - General (Box Box 49)
  - 900.013 ABANDONMENT OF BUS SERVICE (Box Box 49)
  - URRVS 1.1 (Box Box 50)
  - URRVS 1.1 (Box Box 50)
  - URRVS 1.1 (Box Box 50)
  - NOISE ABATEMENT STUDY Reports (Box Box 50)
  - TDC-NOISE STATEMENT STUDY-CORRESPONDENCE (Box Box 50)
  - TDC-NOISE AND VIBRATION RESEARCH AND PROPOSALS (Box Box 50)
  - TDL-RFP TSL/TMP 0187 (Box Box 50)
  - TDC-NOISE AND VIBRATION REPORTS (Box Box 50)
  - TDC-Noise and Vibration Standard Measurements - Correspondence (Box Box 50)
  - RTC Rail Car Standardization - TDC Proposal (Box Box 50)
  - RTC - Rail Car Standardization (Box Box 50)
  - TDC - PROPERTIES RESPONSE AND INPUT (Box Box 50)
  - TDC PROPOSAL (Box Box 50)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 2.2 Project Control (Box Box 50)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 2.1 Project Control Financial Letters (Box Box 50)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 2.2.2 Expense Accounts (Box Box 50)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 3.0 TDC Reports (Box Box 50)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 3.1 Weekly Reports to UMTA (Box Box 50)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 2.0 Administrative (Box Box 50)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 3.4 Pueblo Reports (Box Box 50)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 3.4 Pueblo Reports (Box Box 50)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 3.4 Pueblo Reports (Box Box 50)
  - TDC - MATERIALS CRITERIA AND TESTING PHASE II (Box Box 50)
  - TDC - MATERIALS CRITERIA AND TESTING PHASE II (Box Box 50)
  - TDC - MATERIALS CRITERIA AND TESTING PHASE II (Box Box 50)
  - TDC - MATERIALS CRITERIA AND TESTING PHASE II (Box Box 50)
  - TDC - PROGRAM MATERIALS FLAMMABILITY AND SMOKE (Box Box 50)
  - TDC - PROGRAM MATERIALS FLAMMABILITY AND SMOKE (Box Box 50)
  - TDC - PROGRAM MATERIALS FLAMMABILITY AND SMOKE (Box Box 50)
  - TDC - PROGRAM MATERIALS FLAMMABILITY AND SMOKE /PROFESSOR SMITH USE OF RPT (Box Box 50)
  - TDL - PRELIMINARY RFP TSC/TMP 0173-RN-CORRESPONDENCE (Box Box 50)
  - URRVS PROGRAM 1.2 ACT PRE-AWARD DOCUMENTATION (Box Box 50)
  - 013 APTA Labor Relations Comm. (1 of 3) 1976 (Box Box 51)
  - 013 APTA Labor Relations Comm. (2 of 3) 1976 (Box Box 51)
  - 013 APTA Labor Relations Comm. (3 of 3) 1976 (Box Box 51)
  - MINUTES-EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE TRB - June 11, 1986 (Box Box 51)
  - TRB - EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE MEETING Jan 14, 1986 (Box Box 51)
  - TRANSIT INTERN PROGRAM PROPOSAL 9/20/76 (Box Box 51)
  - 011 GERMAN MARSHALL FUND OF THE UNITED STATES (Box Box 51)
  - TRB-NRC-EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE MEETING June 28th, 1982 (Box Box 51)
  - TRANSPORTATION RESEARCH BOARD (Box Box 51)
  - INSTITUTE OF TRANSPORTATION ENGINEERS (Box Box 51)
  - AASHTO PUBLIC TRANSPORTATION STEERING COMMITTEE (Box Box 51)
  - 1201 NEW YORK AVENUE NW - KAEMPFER (Box Box 51)
  - ASAE EVALUATION REPORT (Box Box 51)
  - 1985 CODE OF ETHICS (Box Box 51)
  - AMERICAN PUBLIC TRANSIT FOUNDATION (Box Box 51)
  - RUDE AWAKENINGS-WASHINTON POST SERIES (Box Box 51)
  - 1996 ANNUAL MEETING EXPO-ATTENDEE RESEARCH (Box Box 51)
  - INTL. PUBLIC TRANSIT EXPOSITION 1999- Sales and Marketing Plan (Box Box 51)
  - INTL. PUBLIC TRANSIT EXPOSITION 1999 Sales and Mktg Plan (Box Box 51)
  - APTA Files (Box Box 51)
  - 13C 1971 - 72 (Box Box 52)
  - 13C-Demo Projects (Box Box 52)
  - 13C - 1978 (Box Box 52)
  - 13C - 1978 (Box Box 52)
  - 13C - 1978 (Box Box 52)
  - 13C AGREEMENTS (Box Box 52)
  - 13-C 1972-1973 (Box Box 52)
  - 13-C 1976 (Box Box 52)
  - 13-C 1976 (Box Box 52)
  - 13-C 1976 (Box Box 52)
  - 13-C 1976 (Box Box 52)
  - 13-C STUDY BY JEFFERSON ASSOCIATES (Box Box 52)
  - CHICAGO TRANSIT AUTHORITY Collective Bargaining Data (Box Box 52)
  - F-13C (Box Box 52)
  - 13(C) (Box Box 52)
  - GENERAL AGREEMENTS (Box Box 52)
  - GENERAL AGREEMENTS (Box Box 52)
  - GENERAL AGREEMENTS (Box Box 52)
  - TRANSIT DATA GROUP (Box Box 52)
  - WASHINGTON JOB PROTECTION AGREEMENT (Box Box 52)
  - 844.1 INTERPRETATIONS (Box Box 53)
  - 844.1 INTERPRETATIONS (Box Box 53)
  - 844.1 INTERPRETATIONS (Box Box 53)
  - 844.1 INTERPRETATIONS (Box Box 53)
  - TRACK CONSTRUCTION (Box Box 53)
  - TRACK CONSTRUCTION MAINTENANCE SUBCOMINICATION (Box Box 53)
  - TRACK CONSTRUCTION AND MAINTENANCE SUBCOMM. (Box Box 53)
  - TRACK CONSTRUCTION AND MAINTENANCE SUBCOMM. (Box Box 53)
  - 840 VENTILATION - SPECIAL TASK FORCE (Box Box 53)
  - 840 TRACK GEOMETRY MEASUREMENT SYSTEM (Box Box 53)
  - 840 MOVING PEOPLE SAFELY AND DESIGN GUIDELINES. (Box Box 53)
  - TRACK CONSTRUCTION AND MAINTENANCE SUBCOMM. (Box Box 53)
  - TRACK CONSTRUCTION AND MAINTENANCE SUBCOMM. (Box Box 53)
  - 840 CONTRACTING PRACTICES REPORT. (Box Box 53)
  - 840 CONTRACTING PRACTICES REPORT. (Box Box 53)
  - 840 APTA RAIL T AND O OPERATIONS COMM (Box Box 53)
  - 1980 RAIL TRANSIT STEERING COMM. MEETING - ATLANTA, GA. (Box Box 53)
  - 1980 RAIL TRANSIT STEERING COMM. MEETING - ATLANTA, GA. (Box Box 53)
  - 840 MISCELLANEOUS. (Box Box 53)
  - '79 MINUTES - RAIL TRANSIT STEERING COMMITTEE. (Box Box 53)
  - MTA ESCROW ARRANGEMENT (Box Box 54)
  - MTA ESCROW ARRANGEMENT (Box Box 54)
  - TRANSIT DEVELOPMENT CORP (Box Box 54)
  - Rail Car Standardization and Rapid Transit (Box Box 54)
  - RAIL CAR STANDARDIZATION AND RAPID TRANSIT (Box Box 54)
  - Computer and ATA (Box Box 54)
  - Computer and ATA (Box Box 54)
  - Computer and ATA (Box Box 54)
  - Update (Box Box 54)
  - Updata (Box Box 54)
  - Update (Box Box 54)
  - Harre Demore Articles 1977 (Box Box 54)
  - Sloan Retirement (Box Box 54)
  - ASAE Evaluation (Box Box 54)
  - 812.1 Executive Comm. Minutes (Hershey) Nov.28,1978 (Box Box 54)
  - 812.1 Executive Comm. MINUTES (Hershey) Nov.28, 1978 (Box Box 54)
  - 001 ASAE Evaluation (Box Box 54)
  - Public Transportation Act of 1978 (Box Box 54)
  - Financial Statements. (Box Box 54)
  - Role of APTA V. Presidents (Box Box 54)
  - Executive Committee Meeting Nov. 29,1978 (Box Box 54)
  - Executive Committee Retreat and Meeting (Box Box 54)
  - Staff Analysis - 1979 Action Agenda (Box Box 54)
  - Discussions of Major Issues facing APTA (Box Box 54)
  - 1978 ASAE APTA Evaluation (Box Box 54)
  - 1978 ASAE APTA Evaluation (Box Box 54)
  - 1978 ASAE APTA Evaluation (Box Box 54)
  - 1978 ASAE APTA Evaluation (Box Box 54)
  - GFC Task Force (Box Box 54)
  - GFC Task Force (Box Box 54)
  - GFC Task Force (Box Box 54)
  - 011.130 NATIONAL INTERN PROGRAM (Box Box 55)
  - 011.130 NATIONAL INTERN PROGRAM (Box Box 55)
  - 011.130 NATIONAL INTERN PROGRAM (Box Box 55)
  - 011.130 NATIONAL INTERN PROGRAM (Box Box 55)
  - 011.130 NATIONAL INTERN PROGRAM (Box Box 55)
  - 011.130 NATIONAL INTERN PROGRAM (Box Box 55)
  - Battery Energy Storage (Box Box 56)
  - BES - X - A (Box Box 56)
  - BES - X - A (Box Box 56)
  - BES - X - C :BES-WES-C (Box Box 56)
  - BES-X-C: BES-AIR-C (Box Box 56)
  - BES - X -C:NYC (Box Box 56)
  - BES-X-C: GH (Box Box 56)
  - BES-X-D (Box Box 56)
  - BES-X-E (Box Box 56)
  - BES-X-M (Box Box 56)
  - BES-X-M (Box Box 56)
  - BES-X-M (Box Box 56)
  - BES-X-R (Box Box 56)
  - BES-X-R (Box Box 56)
  - 3.0 Progress Reports-Monthly (Box Box 56)
  - 3.0 Progress Report-Monthly (Box Box 56)
  - WRRVS DOT-US ACT-1 Design Specification (Box Box 56)
  - SEPTA/ACT-1 Test (Box Box 56)
  - URRVS/STARS:Package for Stars (Box Box 56)
  - RFP-TSC-722-0013 URBAN RAIL SUPPORTING TECHNOLOGY (Box Box 56)
  - RFP-TSC-722-0013 URBAN RAIL SUPPORTING TECHNOLOGY (Box Box 56)
  - 613.861 PROMOTIONAL, SUBSIDIZED FARES (Box Box 57)
  - 613.861 PROMOTIONAL, SUBSIDIZED FARES (Box Box 57)
  - 613.861 PROMOTIONAL, SUBSIDIZED FARES (Box Box 57)
  - 613.92 PASSES, LIMITATIONS (Box Box 57)
  - 615 TRANSIT FARE STRUCTURE (Box Box 57)
  - 615.14 STUDENT FARES (Box Box 57)
  - 615.24 STUDENT FARES (Box Box 57)
  - 615.24 STUDENT FARES (Box Box 57)
  - 615.24 HANDLING AND DISTRIBUTING STUDENT ID CARDS April 25, 1961 (Box Box 57)
  - 615.241 STUDENTS RATE WEEKLY (Box Box 57)
  - CALCULATION OF STUDENT FARES (Box Box 57)
  - 615.24 STUDENT FARES (Box Box 57)
  - 615.24 STUDENT FARES (Box Box 57)
  - 615.24 RESPONSE TO A.T.A. INQUIRY ON STUDENT FARES Circulated August 19, 1968 (Box Box 57)
  - 615.24 STUDENT FARES (Box Box 57)
  - 615.24 STUDENT FARES (Box Box 57)
  - 615.24 STUDENT FARES (Box Box 57)
  - 615.24 STUDENT FARES (Box Box 57)
  - 615.24 STUDENT FARES MISCELLANEOUS (Box Box 57)
  - 900.01 Kandas (General) (Box Box 58)
  - 900.01 Transit District/Bus System Guide (Box Box 58)
  - 900.01 Maine (General) (Box Box 58)
  - RTA Accomplishments (Box Box 58)
  - 900.01 LOUISIANA (GENERAL) (Box Box 58)
  - THE LOUISVILLE RAILWAY COMPANY (Box Box 58)
  - 900.01 MARYLAND(GENERAL) (Box Box 58)
  - 900.01 CALIFORNIA GENERAL (Box Box 58)
  - 900.01 CALIFORNIA (GENERAL) (Box Box 58)
  - 900.01 CALIFORNIA (GENERAL) (Box Box 58)
  - 900.01 TRANSIT SYSTEM PLAN-1988 (Box Box 58)
  - 900.01 WASHINGTON METRO SYSTEM (1986) (Box Box 58)
  - 900.01 AMERICAN TRANSIT COMPANY RESOURCES (Box Box 58)
  - 900.01 HARTFORD, CONN TRANSIT SYSTEM (Box Box 58)
  - 900.01 ARIZONA (GENERAL) (Box Box 58)
  - 900.01 HONOLULU OF TOMORROW (Box Box 58)
  - 900.01 HAWAII (GENERAL) (Box Box 58)
  - 900.01 CCT BUS SYSTEM INFORMATION (Box Box 58)
  - 900.01 TRANSIT GUIDES, LOUISVILLE TRANSIT COMPANY (Box Box 58)
  - 900.01 ILLINOIS (GENERAL) (Box Box 58)
  - 900.01 ILLINOIS (GENERAL) (Box Box 58)
  - 900.01 ILLINOIS (GENERAL) (Box Box 58)
  - 900.01 Florida (Box Box 58)
  - 900.01 Florida (Box Box 58)
  - Transit and Transportation Directory (Box Box 58)
  - 900.01 Connecticut (Box Box 58)
  - Traffic Study and Predictions (Box Box 58)
  - Public Transportation in Arizona (Box Box 58)
  - Transit Authority/Transit District (Box Box 58)
  - FARE TASK IV REPORT (Box Box 59)
  - Fare Task IV Report (Box Box 59)
  - Fare Task IV Report (Box Box 59)
  - Commuter Rail (Box Box 59)
  - Fare Project and Orientation (Box Box 59)
  - Fare Project and Orientation (Box Box 59)
  - Index of Expense Reporting Documentation (Box Box 59)
  - 078.66 FARE Project 1975 (Box Box 59)
  - 078.66 FARE Project 1975 (Box Box 59)
  - 078.66 FARE Project 1975 (Box Box 59)
  - FARE PROJECT 71-72 (Box Box 59)
  - FARE - ATA REPORTS (Box Box 59)
  - PROJECT FARE (Box Box 59)
  - PROJECT FARE (Box Box 59)
  - PROJECT FARE (Box Box 59)
  - PROJECT FARE (Box Box 59)
  - PROJECT FARE (Box Box 59)
  - PROJECT FARE (Box Box 59)
  - PROJECT FARE (Box Box 59)
  - 415.8 OPERATING PERFORMANCE (Box Box 60)
  - 415.8 OPERATING PERFORMANCE/ANTIFREEZE (Box Box 60)
  - 415.8 OPERATING PERFORMANCE/ AIR BRAKES (Box Box 60)
  - 415.8312 SANDS, SALT, CINDERS, ETC (Box Box 60)
  - 416.1 ELECTRIC LOCOMOTIVE SYSTEMS (Box Box 60)
  - 417 A.T.A. ESTIMATES (Box Box 60)
  - 417 TROLLY BUS ARTICLES/OPERATIONS (Box Box 60)
  - 417 TROLLEY COACH DESIGN (Box Box 60)
  - 417.023 AIR CONDITIONING OF TROLLEY-COACHES (Box Box 60)
  - 417.03 LIGHTING, INTERIOR (Box Box 60)
  - 417.0031 AGE OF TROLLEY BUSES (Box Box 60)
  - 417.13 TROLLEY BUS AXLES (Box Box 60)
  - 417.5 TROLLEY COACH POWER DISTRIBUTION SYSTEM (Box Box 60)
  - 417.52 OVERHEAD TROLLEY COACH CONSTRUCTION (Box Box 60)
  - 417.524 RETRIEVERS (Box Box 60)
  - 432 BETTER MAINTENANCE METHODS-LOWER COSTS (Box Box 60)
  - 432.01 SMALL OPERATIONS STEERING COMMITTEE REPORT (Box Box 60)
  - 432.002 OTTAWA TRANSPORTATION COMMISSION Job Specifications and Procedures (Box Box 60)
  - 432.101 CLEANING OF TRANSIT BUSES (Box Box 60)
  - 432.102 LABOUR STATISTICS (Box Box 60)
  - 432.103 INFO.REGARDING HOT SPRAY PAINT (Box Box 60)
  - 432.021 BUS PITS VS. BUS LIFTS (Box Box 60)
  - 432.032 RATIO OF SPARE MOTOR BUSES (Box Box 60)
  - 432.043 DIESEL MAINTENANCE PRACTICES (Box Box 60)
  - 432.053 JOB ORDER COST SYSTEMS (Box Box 60)
  - 432.063 HOISTS-DOLLIES (Box Box 60)
  - 432.21 SUPPORTING FRAMES ON CHASSIS (Box Box 60)
  - 432.28 BRAKES (Box Box 60)
  - 432.280.1 AIR BRAKE MAINTENANCE (Box Box 60)
  - 432.29 WHEELS AND TIRES (Box Box 60)
  - 432.3 PAINTING BUSES AND OVERHAULING ENGINES (Box Box 60)
  - 432.301 USE OF DYNAMOMETERS (Box Box 60)
  - 432.43 BATTERIES (Box Box 60)
  - 432.502 FUEL STORAGE INQUIRY 8-28-72 (Box Box 60)
  - 432.701 LUBRICANTS (Box Box 60)
  - 432.702.1 SPECTROMETRIC ANALYSIS OF OIL (Box Box 60)
  - 432.902 OUTSIDE MAINTENANCE (Box Box 60)
  - 432.903 ROADSIDE REPAIRS, MOTOR BUS EQUIPMENT (Box Box 60)
  - 432.904.2 TRUCK MAINTENANCE (Box Box 60)
  - FLEET OWNER-MAINTENANCE EFFICIENCY AWARDS 1966 (Box Box 60)
  - FLEET OWNER-MAINTENANCE EFFICIENCY AWARDS 1966 (Box Box 60)
  - PROPOSAL # DOT-UT-20008 Pt.1 DISSERTATION (Box Box 61)
  - INTERIM TASK 111 REPORT (Nov '72 - June '73) (Box Box 61)
  - 840 Rapid Transit Construction (Box Box 62)
  - 840 Rapid Transit Construction (Box Box 62)
  - 840 Rapid Transit Construction (Box Box 62)
  - 840 Rapid Transit Construction (Box Box 62)
  - 840 Rapid Transit Construction (Box Box 62)
  - 840 Rapid Transit Construction (Box Box 62)
  - 814.816 BUS TECHNOLOGY (Box Box 62)
  - 814.816 BUS TECHNOLOGY (Box Box 62)
  - 814.816 BUS TECHNOLOGY (Box Box 62)
  - 840 POWER AND SIGNALS (Box Box 62)
  - 840 POWER AND SIGNALS (Box Box 62)
  - 840 POWER AND SIGNALS (Box Box 62)
  - 840 POWER AND SIGNALS (Box Box 62)
  - 840 LIGHT RAIL SYSTEMS (Box Box 62)
  - 840 LIGHT RAIL SYSTEMS (Box Box 62)
  - 840 LIGHT RAIL SYSTEMS (Box Box 62)
  - 840 LIGHT RAIL SYSTEMS (Box Box 62)
  - 840 PUBLICATIONS COMMITTEE (Box Box 62)
  - 840 PUBLICATIONS COMMITTEE (Box Box 62)
  - 840 PUBLICATIONS COMMITTEE (Box Box 62)
  - 840 NOISE AND VIBRATION (Box Box 62)
  - 840 NOISE AND VIBRATION (Box Box 62)
  - 840 SAFETY TECHNOLOGY (Box Box 62)
  - 840 SAFETY TECHNOLOGY (Box Box 62)
  - 840 SAFETY TECHNOLOGY (Box Box 62)
  - 840 SAFETY TECHNOLOGY (Box Box 62)
  - 840 RELIABILITY, MAINTAINABILITY, AVAILABILITY (Box Box 62)
  - 840 RELIABILITY, MAINTAINABILITY, AVAILABILITY (Box Box 62)
  - 840 RELIABILITY, MAINTAINABILITY, AVAILABILITY (Box Box 62)
  - 075.1 SAFETY-HOURS OF SERVICE (Box Box 63)
  - 075.1 SAFETY - HOURS OF SERVICE (Box Box 63)
  - 075.201 SIZES AND WEIGHTS-RESTRICTIONS (Box Box 63)
  - 075.201 SIZES AND WEIGHTS-RESTRICTIONS (Box Box 63)
  - 075.62 STATE REGULATIONS ON TROLLEY BUSES (Box Box 63)
  - 075.62 STATE REGULATIONS ON TROLLEY BUSES (Box Box 63)
  - 075.62 STATE REGULATIONS ON TROLLEY BUSES (Box Box 63)
  - 075.62 STATE REGULATIONS ON TROLLEY BUSES (Box Box 63)
  - 075.62 STATE REGULATIONS ON TROLLEY BUSES (Box Box 63)
  - 075.62 STATE REGULATIONS ON TROLLEY BUSES (Box Box 63)
  - 814.816 BUS TECHNOLOGY (Box Box 63)
  - 814.816 BUS TECHNOLOGY (Box Box 63)
  - 814.816 BUS TECHNOLOGY (Box Box 63)
  - 814.816 BUS TECHNOLOGY (Box Box 63)
  - 814.816 BUS TECHNOLOGY (Box Box 63)
  - 814.816 BUS TECHNOLOGY (Box Box 63)
  - 814.816 BUS TECHNOLOGY (Box Box 63)
  - 814.816 BUS TECHNOLOGY (Box Box 63)
  - 814.816 BUS TECHNOLOGY (Box Box 63)
  - 814.816 BUS TECHNOLOGY (Box Box 63)
  - 814.816 BUS TECHNOLOGY (Box Box 63)
  - 814.816 BUS TECHNOLOGY (Box Box 63)
  - 814.816 BUS TECHNOLOGY (Box Box 63)
  - AMERICAN TRANSIT ASSN. #400 (Box Box 64)
  - AMERICAN TRANSIT ASSN. #400 (Box Box 64)
  - AMERICAN TRANSIT ASSN. #400 (Box Box 64)
  - 400 ATA EQUIPMENT ESTIMATES (Box Box 64)
  - 400.053 SPARE VEHICLES (Box Box 64)
  - 400.22 PURCHASE PRICES-COMPARED EQP. (Box Box 64)
  - 411 TABULATIONS-CAR STATISTICS (Box Box 64)
  - 1951 VEHICLE REQUIREMENTS FOR THE TRANSIT INDUSTRY (Box Box 64)
  - FUTURE DEMAND FOR NEW AND REBUILT BUSES (Box Box 64)
  - COMMITTEE ON MOTOR COACHES AND PASSENGER VEHICLE DESIGN (Box Box 64)
  - 415.001 STATISTICS-TRANSIT SYSTEM SIZE (Box Box 64)
  - 415.011 SMALL BUSES AND MINI-BUSES (Box Box 64)
  - 415.014 SPECIAL ENQUIRY SERVICE-SCHOOL BUSES (Box Box 64)
  - SURVEY-NEW STANDARDS FOE SCHOOL BUSES (Box Box 64)
  - SURVEY-NEW STANDARDS FOR SCHOOL BUSES (Box Box 64)
  - SURVEY-NEW STANDARDS FOR SCHOOL BUSES (Box Box 64)
  - SURVEY-NEW STANDARDS FOR SCHOOL BUSES (Box Box 64)
  - SURVEY-NEW STANDARDS FOR SCHOOL BUSES (Box Box 64)
  - SURVEY-NEW STANDARDS FOR SCHOOL BUSES (Box Box 64)
  - SURVEY-NEW STANDARDS FOR SCHOOL BUSES (Box Box 64)
  - SURVEY-NEW STANDARDS FOR SCHOOL BUSES (Box Box 64)
  - SURVEY-NEW STANDARDS FOR SCHOOL BUSES (Box Box 64)
  - SURVEY-NEW STANDARDS FOR SCHOOL BUSES (Box Box 64)
  - SURVEY-NEW STANDARDS FOR SCHOOL BUSES (Box Box 64)
  - SURVEY-NEW STANDARDS FOR SCHOOL BUSES (Box Box 64)
  - SURVEY-NEW STANDARDS FOR SCHOOL BUSES (Box Box 64)
  - 415.014 SCHOOL BUSES (Box Box 64)
  - 415.014 SCHOOL BUSES (Box Box 64)
  - 615.6 FARE PLAN (Box Box 65)
  - 615.9 PURCHASE, SALE OF TICKETS, TOKENS (Box Box 65)
  - 616 TRANSFERS-GENERAL (Box Box 65)
  - 616.11 ADVERTISING ON BACK OF TRANSFERS (Box Box 65)
  - 616.6 CHARGE FOR TRANSFERS (Box Box 65)
  - 616.62 TRANSFERS FOR STUDENTS (Box Box 65)
  - 300.4 TRANSIT DEVELOPMENT CORP (Box Box 66)
  - 300.4 TRANSIT DEVELOPMENT CORP (Box Box 66)
  - 300.4 T.D.C. 1974 (Box Box 66)
  - 300.4 T.D.C. 1974 (Box Box 66)
  - NATIONAL SCIENCE FOUNDATION (Box Box 66)
  - 300.4 TDC 1975-76 (Box Box 66)
  - 300.4 TDC 1975-76 (Box Box 66)
  - 300.4 TDC 1975-76 (Box Box 66)
  - 300.4 TDC 1975-76 (Box Box 66)
  - TDC AND SMALL BUS 300.4 (Box Box 66)
  - REPORT OF EXAMINATION TDC FOR YEAR ENDED JUNE 30, 1974 (Box Box 66)
  - 300.4 T.D.C. 1975 (Box Box 66)
  - 300.4 T.D.C. 1975 (Box Box 66)
  - 300.4 T.D.C. 1975 (Box Box 66)
  - 300.4 T.D.C. 1975 (Box Box 66)
  - 300.4 T.D.C. 1975 (Box Box 66)
  - 300.4 T.D.C. 1975 (Box Box 66)
  - PROGRAM PLANNING MANUAL #015 (Box Box 66)
  - ROBERT SLOAN #049 (Box Box 66)
  - 900.01 NEW YORK TRANSIT (Box Box 67)
  - 900.01 NEW YORK TRANSIT (Box Box 67)
  - 900.01 NEW YORK TRANSIT (Box Box 67)
  - 900.01 MADISON AVENUE (Box Box 67)
  - 900.01 STEINWAY TRANSIT CORP. (Box Box 67)
  - 900.01 STEINWAY TRANSIT CORP. (Box Box 67)
  - 900.01 MADISON AVENUE (Box Box 67)
  - REPLIES (Box Box 68)
  - REPLIES (Box Box 68)
  - BUS TURNOUTS (Box Box 68)
  - REPLIES (Box Box 68)
  - PASSENGERS (Box Box 68)
  - GRAPHICS (Box Box 68)
  - REPLIES (Box Box 68)
  - REPLIES (Box Box 68)
  - RE: UNIFICATION OF B.M.T. - B.Q.T. Properties June 1939 (Box Box 69)
  - 900 N.Y. WORLDS FAIR (Box Box 69)
  - 900 N.Y. WORLDS (Box Box 69)
  - 900 NEW JERSEY PUBLIC SERVICE (Box Box 69)
  - 900 MINNESOTA (Box Box 69)
  - 900 N.Y.C. GENERAL (Box Box 69)
  - 900 N.Y.C. GENERAL (Box Box 69)
  - 900 MISSOURI B1-STATE (Box Box 69)
  - 900 MISSOUSI B1-STATE (Box Box 69)
  - 900(MO) ST. LOUIS PUBLIC SERVICE CO. (Box Box 69)
  - 900 NYC-MANHATTAN PR. (Box Box 69)
  - 900 PATH (Box Box 69)
  - 900 NYC QUEENS (Box Box 69)
  - 900 2nd AVENUE (Box Box 69)
  - 900 NEW YORK CITY (Box Box 69)
  - 900 ST. LOUIS PUBLIC SERVICE CO. (Box Box 69)
  - 900 EIGHTH AVENUE (Box Box 69)
  - 900 NYC TRANSIT SYSTEM (Box Box 69)
  - 900 PORT AUTHORITY OF NY (Box Box 69)
  - MAPS/MISCELLANEOUS BROCHURES (Box Box 69)
  - 900 KANSAS CITY MO (Box Box 69)
  - 900 KANSAS CITY MO (Box Box 69)
  - 900 MASS BOSTON (Box Box 69)
  - 900 MASS BOSTON (Box Box 69)
  - 900 MASS BOSTON (Box Box 69)
  - 900 MICHIGAN (Box Box 69)
  - NEW YORK CITY TRANSIT AUTHORITY (Box Box 69)
  - 900.01 ALABAMA (Box Box 69)
  - AMERICAN ELECTRIC RAILWAY (Box Box 69)
  - 073.1 CHICAGO TRANSIT AUTHORITY (Box Box 70)
  - 073.1 INDIANA TRANSIT (Box Box 70)
  - 073.1 KENTUCKY, MARYLAND TRANSIT (Box Box 70)
  - 073 MASS-STATE TRANSIT SYSTEM (Box Box 70)
  - 073.1 MASS-STATE TRANSIT SYSTEM (Box Box 70)
  - 073.1 BI - State Transit System (Box Box 70)
  - 073.1 State Transit (Box Box 70)
  - 073.11 PUBLIC CONTRACTS FOR TRANSIT SERVICE (Box Box 70)
  - FEDERAL 074.32 MOTOR FUEL TAXES (Box Box 70)
  - 074.34 OIL - DIESEL OIL TAX (Box Box 70)
  - 075.412 SOLICITATION OF POTENTIAL TRANSIT PASSENGERS (Box Box 70)
  - 075.413 CAR POOLS - SHARE EXPENSE TRAVEL BUREAU (Box Box 70)
  - 078.201 BUREAU OF FEDERAL BUDGET (Box Box 70)
  - 078.23 U.S. SAVINGS BONDS AND STAMPS (Box Box 70)
  - 078.24 FOREIGN EXCHANGE REGULATIONS (Box Box 70)
  - 078.556 ICC - GENERAL (Box Box 70)
  - 078.556 LISTS - ICC (Box Box 70)
  - 078.31, 078.551, 078.63, 078.82 ENERGY, POWER, ENVIRONMENT (Box Box 70)
  - 091 RAILROADS-MISCELLANEOUS (Box Box 70)
  - 093 AUTOMOBILES (Box Box 70)
  - 094.1 ATOMIC POWER - ATOMIC RADIATION, ETC. (Box Box 70)
  - TEXAS TRANSIT CONFERENCES 3/23 - 24/76 - 3/10 (Box Box 71)
  - 001 TRB GENERAL (Box Box 71)
  - 001 TRB GENERAL (Box Box 71)
  - INDIANA BUS ASSOCIATION (Box Box 71)
  - INSTITUTE OF TRAFFIC ENGINEERS (Box Box 71)
  - NATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF MOTOR BUS OPERATIONS (Box Box 71)
  - Pennsylvania Bus Association (Box Box 71)
  - New York City Bus Conference (Box Box 71)
  - Pitts. Urban Transit Council (Box Box 71)
  - Private Bus Operator's Conference (Box Box 71)
  - 001 Public Interest Group Luncheon (Box Box 71)
  - 001 Railway Progress Inst. (Box Box 71)
  - Society of Automotive Engineers (Box Box 71)
  - Society of Automotive Engineers (Box Box 71)
  - N.Y. State Motor Bus Assoc. (Box Box 71)
  - N.Y. State Motor Bus Assoc. (Box Box 71)
  - Ohio Public Transit Assoc. (Box Box 71)
  - Oil International Labs, Inc. (Box Box 71)
  - 001 National Recreation Access Study (Box Box 71)
  - National Research Council (Box Box 71)
  - New England Transit Club (Box Box 71)
  - American Road Builders Association (Box Box 71)
  - American Society of Associate Executives (Box Box 71)
  - (Box Box 71)
  - (Box Box 71)
  - (Box Box 71)